我帮你们准备了一份礼物
Hey, I got you a present!
天啊 你把它藏在哪里
Oh, my goodness, where did you hide it?
我订了它当做你们结婚的礼物 它终于被送来了
I got it for your wedding, I ordered it weeks ago and it finally got here!
你不必送我们任何…
Pheebs, you didn't have to get us anything for our...
我喜欢它 它很大 我们打开它吧
I love it! It's huge! Let's open it! Open it!
- 是小精灵的电动   - 我的天啊
- It's a Ms. Pac-Man machine!     - Oh, my God!
我不知道该放到哪里去 所以就把它留在这
I didn't know where to put it so I left.
- 我们可以把它放在客房   - 好吧
- We can put it in the guest bedroom.     - Yeah, okay.
- 我喜欢把它放在这里   - 你真的喜欢它吗
- I kind of like it here.     - Do you really like it?
你在开玩笑吗 我小时候都待在游乐场里
Are you kidding? I practically spent my entire childhood at the arcade.
- 这是我第二喜欢的游戏   - 你最喜欢什么
- This was, like, my second favorite game.     - What was your first?
- 我记不得它的名字了   - 它的内容是什么
- I don't really remember the name of it.     - Well, what did it do?
把铜板放进去 一拉把手 就能拿到糖果
Well, you'd put a quarter in, pull some handles and win a candy bar.
自动贩卖机
A vending machine?
别为我难过 每次我都会赢
Hey, don't feel bad for me. I won every time!
# 没有人告诉你活着有多累 #
# So no one told you life was gonna be this way #
# 上班受罪 口袋空空 爱情变累赘 #
# Your job's a joke, you're broke, your love life's D.O.A. #
# 寂寞又潦倒 受气又受累 #
# It's like you're always stuck in second gear #
# 日复一日 年复一年 #
# When it hasn't been your day, #
# 时运不济 活着受罪 #
# your week, your month, or even your year #
# 你我永不离弃 #
# but I'll be there for you #
# 你我相偎相依 #
# 'Cause you're there for me too #
我很高兴你们都在
Hey! I'm so glad you guys are here.
我等不及告诉你们古生物系发生了什么事
I've been dying to tell someone what happened in the paleontology department.
你觉得他看到了我们 还是我们有机会落跑
Do you think he saw us, or can we still slip out?
系主任诺曼教授要退休了 所以…
Professor Newman, the head of the department, is retiring, so...
- 他们让你当系主任   - 我要教他的高级课
- They made you head of the department!     - No, I get to teach his advanced class!
我为什么没有当上系主任
Why didn't I get head of the department?
- 瑞秋 听着…   - 嗯
- Oh, hey, Rach, listen, um...     - Yeah.
我有个重要约会 你知道哪家餐厅不错吗
I got a big date. Do you know a good restaurant?
保罗咖啡厅 那里东西好吃 气氛真的很浪漫
Uh, Paul's Cafe. It's got great food and it's really romantic.
太棒了 谢谢
Ooh. Great, thanks.
然后带她到四季饭店喝东西
And then after, you could take her to the Four Seasons for drinks.
或是到城里听爵士乐
Or go downtown and listen to some jazz.
或跳舞 带她去跳舞
Or dancing. Oh, take her dancing!
你真的很会拖延性爱游戏
You sure are naming a lot of ways to postpone sex, I'll tell you.
我想念约会的感觉 盛装打扮去好餐厅吃饭
Agh, I miss dating. Getting dressed up, going to a fancy restaurant.
我很久都无法再那么做了 那真的很有趣
I'm not gonna be able to do that for so long. And it's so much fun.
我不是说坐在这里 担心生产的事不好玩
Not that sitting at home worrying about giving birth to a 16-pound baby is not fun.
知道吗 我们为什么不去约会
Hey, you know what? Why don't I take you out?
什么 你才不想跟孕妇约会
What? You don't want to go on a date with a pregnant lady.
我想我们会玩得很开心
Yes, I do. We're gonna go out, we're gonna have a good time.
我会让你忘了生孩子 剖腹生产…
I'll take your mind off of childbirth, and C-sections...
宝宝的头扩大了…
...and giant baby heads stretching out...
好吧 我答应你
Okay, I'll go with you. I'll go.
- 那会很好玩的   - 好吧
- It will be fun.     - All right. Okay.
不 太棒了
No, no! Yes!
快来看
Aw, would you look at that, Monica?
我打败了你的最佳成绩 太惨了
I knocked off all your top scores. How sad.
好吧 轮到我了
Okay, I'm next.
别再开始 轮到我了 菲比
No, don't start another game. I'm next! Phoebe?
抱歉 我赢得太开心 听不到你说话
I'm sorry, I couldn't hear you over all the winning.
- 菲比在霸占游戏   - 谁在乎啊 那是个愚蠢的游戏
- Chandler! Phoebe's hogging the game.     - Who cares? It's a stupid game.
你觉得它蠢 因为你很逊
Oh, you only think it's stupid because you suck at it.
我不逊 它才逊
I don't suck. It sucks.
你很逊
You suck.
如果这游戏会引起你们的困扰
If this game is gonna cause problems between you...
- 我应该留下它   - 不 我喜欢它 它是很棒的礼物
...maybe I should keep it.     - No, I love it. It is a great present.
你为什么不回家等贺卡呢
In fact, why don't you go home and wait for the "Thank You" card?
- 你为什么要玩这个游戏   - 对啊 玩完之后又不会…
- Why do you want to play so badly?     - Yeah, it's not like it spits out...
吐出糖果
...a Clark Bar after every game.
好吧 菲比 够了 快下来
Okay. Phoebe, that's it. Out of the chair. Come on. Out of the chair.
菲比
Phoebe!
乔伊 麻烦你去开门
Joey, could you get that?
乔伊
Ugh, Joey...
你这是干嘛  我以为你在房里
What? I thought you were in your room.
我是来接你的 这是送你的
No, I'm picking you up for our date. These are for you.
百合花 它们是我最喜欢的花 谢谢
Oh, lilies. They're my favorite. Thank you.
还有布朗尼
And a brownie.
只有一半
Well, half a brownie.
事实上它只剩袋子
Actually, it's just a bag.
从花店走回来真的很远 我觉得头晕 所以…
It's a long walk from the flower shop and I was starting to feel faint, so...
这真的是太棒了
Oh, man, this is so great!
我觉得好像真的在约会
I actually feel like I'm going on a real date.
但我会害喜 我穿的内裤裤头高到…
With a hint of morning sickness and I'm wearing underwear that goes up to about...
这里
...there.
少来了 这是真的约会
Hey, come on. This is a real date. Uh...
你家好漂亮
So, nice place you got here.
桌上足球 比萨盒
Foosball, huh? Pizza box.
还有"花花公子"杂志 你是我喜欢的那种女人
Oh, a subscription to Playboy. My kind of woman.
那是我室友的杂志
Actually, that's my roommate's.
我想见见他 他似乎是个好男人
I'd like to meet him. He sounds like a standup guy.
他很保护我
But he's very protective of me...
你最好小心一点
...so you'd better watch yourself.
你室友很帅吗
Hey, so, this roommate of yours, is he good-looking?
是吗
Oh, yeah.
你一定很努力控制自己不爱上他
Must be tough to keep your hands off him.
我相信他是男同志
Yeah, but I'm pretty sure he's gay.
不是的 你为什么要毁了这个游戏
No! No, he's not! Why are you trying to ruin the game?
这让我想起葛瑞利的骨牌理论
Which brings us back, of course, to Greely's Theory of Dominance.
今天到此为止
That's it for today.
有人知道费利曼楼在哪里吗
Oh, uh, does anyone know where the Freeman Building is?
那是A大道的新大楼
Yeah, it's the new building on Avenue A.
它在城里的另一边
What? That's across town.
我10分钟内得赶到那里上课
I'm supposed to teach a seminar there in 10 minutes.
那是不可能的
Ooh, dude, that's not gonna happen.
快闪开
Move it. Move it. Move it!
我是老师
Hey! I'm the teacher!
哈罗
Hello.
抱歉我迟到了
Sorry I'm a little late. Uh...
我严重迟到
Whoa, a lot late.
我从自我介绍开始吧
Uh, well, let me start by, uh, introducing myself.
我是盖勒教授
I'm, uh, Professor Geller.
总而言之…
So to sum up...
我是盖勒教授 今天大家做得很好
...I'm Professor Geller. Good job today.
菲力牛排搭配什么
Now, the filet mignon, what comes with that?
蒸蔬菜
A side of steamed vegetables.
除了蔬菜…
Instead of the vegetables...
我可以用什么东西搭配…
...is there any way that I could substitute the, um...
三磅的龙虾
...three-pound lobster?
知道吗 帮她把两道菜都送上来
You know what? Bring her both.
我要点跟她一样的东西
And I'll have the same.
这真的是个很棒的约会
Wow, this is shaping up to be a pretty good date.
我差点忘了 我没给你房租
Oh, I almost forgot. I didn't pay you the rent.
别当我们是室友 我们在约会
Whoa, whoa, whoa, no roommate stuff. We're on a date.
我想知道乔伊·崔比亚尼怎么跟女人约会
Okay. Wow, so I get to see what Joey Tribbiani is like on a date.
你有什么招数
Do you have any moves?
不 我只会做我自己 如果她们不喜欢我…
No, I'm just myself, and if they don't like me for...
抱歉 我无法想像那种事
I'm sorry, I couldn't even get through that.
我就知道 告诉我你有什么招数
I knew it. Come on, tell me your moves.
好吧
Uh, all right. Um...
嗯…
Well...
我会假装有影迷送一瓶红酒给我们
I start by having a bottle of wine sent to my table from a fan.
天啊 有用吗
Oh, my God. And that works?
你得加上"这真是太不好意思了
It does when you combine it with, "This is embarrassing.
我只想过正常人的生活"
I just want to have a normal life."
你们这些可怜的名人
Aw, you poor little famous man.
好吧 这个呢
Oh, okay, how about this one?
我本来想等到送你回家再吻你…
I was gonna wait until the end of the night to kiss you...
但你真的太美了 我想我做不到
...but you're just so beautiful, I don't think I can.
天啊
Oh, my God! Ha.
那真的太棒了 我差点就被你骗了
Wow, that was fantastic! I almost leaned in. I really almost did.
告诉我你用的是什么招数
All right, so tell me one of your moves.
好吧
All right. Ahem.
你是在哪里长大的
So where'd you grow up?
那就是你的招数
That's your move?
瑞秋 还好你长得很美
Boy, Rach, you're lucky you're hot.
- 快回答我的问题   - 皇后区
- Come on, just answer the question.     - Ugh. Queens.
你跟父母亲近吗
And so were you close to your parents?
- 我跟妈妈亲 跟爸爸不太说话   - 为什么
- With my mom. Not so much my dad.     - Why not?
我不知道 我们之间有距离
I don't know. I guess there's just always been this distance.
我们都假装没有 但事实上不然
I mean, we both try to pretend it's not there, but it is.
那一定很辛苦
It's gotta be rough.
对 那真的很辛苦 有时候我认为…
It is. Yeah, it's really tough. You know, sometimes I think...
太帅了
Nice move!
- "你在哪里长大的 " 太简单了   - 谢谢
- "Where'd you grow up?" So simple.     - Thank you.
对不起 我要去洗手间
Ha, ha. Now, excuse me. I'm gonna go to the restroom.
- 你正看着我走开   - 没错 太简单了
- And now you're watching me walk away.     - Yes, I am! Again, so simple.
嗨
Hey.
你一定不相信今天我做了什么
You're not gonna believe what I did today.
很明显地你没洗澡或刮胡子
Clearly wasn't showering or shaving.
我变厉害了 我玩了一整天 现在我是第一名
I got good. I played this game all day, and now I rule at it.
他们应该把它改名为 "钱德小姐"
They should change the name of it to "Ms. Chandler."
还是不要好了
Although, I hope they don't.
你待在家里玩小精灵
You stayed home all day and played Ms. Pac-Man...
我出门像牛一样在工作
...while I went off to work like some chump?
我包办了前10名 把菲比给挤掉了 庆祝一下吧
Uh-huh. I got the top ten scores. I erased Phoebe off the board. High-five!
你的手是怎么了
What is the matter with your hand?
我打了八小时的电动
I been playing for eight hours.
它会放松的 看看我的记录
It'll loosen up. Come on, check out the scores.
看看我编的名字 它们全是脏话
And also, look at the initials. They're dirty words.
- 钱德 你为什么要那么做    - 因为它很棒
- Chandler, why would you do that?     - Because it's awesome.
你觉得那么做很聪明
You think this is clever?
我只能写下三个字母 除了屁股外 其他的可是个大挑战
They only give you three letters, so after A-S-S, it is a challenge.
- 这不是脏话   - 把它跟那个连在一起
- This one's not dirty.     - It is when you put it together with that one.
如果你没办法把它清掉 我不会答应你的
If you don't clear this off, you won't get one of those from me.
小班明天会过来 不能让他看到这个
Ben's coming over here tomorrow. This can't be there.
- 他不知道它们的意思   - 他七岁了 他不笨
- He won't know what they mean.     - He's 7, not stupid.
- 最近你跟他谈过吗    - 我要把插头拔掉
- Have you talked to him lately?     - Look, I'm gonna unplug it.
我没办法证明我今天做了什么
No, no! I'll have nothing to show for my day.
就跟我的工作一样
It'll be like I was at work.
不
No!
你看 画面还在
Hey, look! It's still there!
这玩意一定是用原始的记忆晶片
This thing must have some kind of primitive ROM chip in it or something!
- 你得打败自己的成绩   - 我的手指都张不开了
- You gotta beat your scores.     - With the claw?
好吧 让我来 我们得把这个消掉
Fine, I'll do it. We gotta get this off the screen.
卡萝还在气你教他"拉我的手指"
Carol's still upset that you taught him "Pull my finger."
拉我的手指 我的手毁了
Pull my finger. My hand is messed up!
- 我不会回答那个问题   - 来吧 快挑一个
- I am not gonna answer that.     - Oh, come on. Just pick one.
在摩妮卡 菲比 钱德跟罗斯之问…
Between Monica, Phoebe, Chandler and Ross...
如果你非那么做不可 你会打谁
...if you had to... If you had to, who would you punch?
谁都不打 我们是朋友 我不会打他们
No one. They're my friends. I wouldn't punch any of them.
钱德吗
Chandler?
对 但我不知道为什么
Yeah, but I don't know why.
- 我玩得很开心   - 我也是
- I'm having a wonderful time!     - Me too.
瑞秋 我只想说…
Hey, Rach, can I just say...
- 这是我最棒的约会经验   - 我知道
...I think this is the best date I ever had.     - I know!
我笑得好厉害 你看到酒从我鼻子喷出来吗
I've never laughed so hard. Did you see the wine come out my nose?
乔伊 我想大家都看到了
Yes. Joey, I think everybody saw the wine come out of your nose.
我不知道我会这么喜欢没有性爱的约会
I gotta say, I never knew I could enjoy the non-sex part of a date so much.
那是因为你没有跟我约会过
That's because you have never been on a date with me before.
好吧 别批评我
All right. Now don't judge me.
通常我会等我的对象离开了再这么做 但你住这里
I normally wait till my date leaves, but you live here.
我要把剩菜吃了
I'm ripping into the swan.
好吧 你也别批评我
Okay, well then, you don't judge me.
我要去舔布朗尼的包装纸
I'm gonna suck on the cellophane from the brownie I had before.
告诉我 乔伊·崔比亚尼说晚安的招数是什么
So tell me, what are Joey Tribbiani's end-of-the-night moves?
如果我要那个女孩吻我…
Uh, well, if I want the girl to kiss me...
首先我会让我的嘴巴看起来难以抵抗
...first thing I do is make my lips look irresistible.
你都是怎么做的
How do you do it?
你不能告诉任何人 但是…
Now you can't tell anyone, but, uh...
我会涂上护唇膏
...I put on shiny lip balm.
- 天啊   - 女人就跟飞蛾扑火一样
- Oh, my God.     - Like a moth to a flame, I'm telling you.
- 好吧 轮到你了   - 不 我不想告诉你
- Okay, all right, so now you go.     - No, I don't want to tell you.
- 为什么    - 那太丢脸了
- Why not?     - It's embarrassing.
比涂覆盆子口味的护唇膏还丢脸
More embarrassing than shiny raspberry lip balm?
我刚刚没说覆盆子口味吧
I didn't say raspberry before, did I?
快告诉我 瑞秋
Just tell me, Rach. Just tell me.
好吧 站起来
Okay. All right, stand up.
我们走到门边时…
Well, when we're at the door...
我会将我的嘴唇轻轻压在他的嘴唇上
...I lightly press my lips against his.
将身体靠向他一秒钟
Then move into his body, just for a second.
然后我会发出这样的声音
And then I make this sound:
听起来没什么 但很有效
I know it doesn't sound like anything, but it works.
对 那的确有效
Oh, yeah. That would work, yeah.
好吧 我得睡了 我玩得很开心
All right, I gotta go to bed. I had such a wonderful time.
是啊
Oh, yeah.
我也是
Me too.
你迟到了 50分钟 你是用爬的吗
You were 50 minutes late to the class? Did you crawl there?
不 我用跑的 那真的很远
No, I ran, okay? It's really far.
人们什么时候开始听不懂 "别挡我的路"
When did people stop understanding "Get the hell out of my way"?
你为什么不搭计程车
Why didn't you take a cab?
塞车太严重 那是单行道 搭计程车得花两倍的时间
Ugh. Between the traffic and one-way streets, it'd take me twice as long.
我一星期有三堂课 我是洛克菲勒吗
Besides, I teach the class three times a week. Who am I, Rockefeller?
你没办法再继续下去
You're not gonna be able to keep doing this.
我不那么做 他们会取消我这堂课
I have to. If I don't, they'll take the class away from me.
我把它登在我家的通讯报上
And I already put it in my family newsletter.
- 什么    - 你看过的 "盖勒通讯报"
- Your what?     - You've seen it, The Geller Yeller.
对
Right. Wow.
我想出一条比较快的路线 我想这次我能及时赶到
Besides, I figured out a faster route. I'm sure I can make it this time.
我不能害怕被车子撞到
I just can't be afraid to get a little bit hit by cars.
- 嘿   - 嗨
- Hey.     - Hi!
还记得我们谈过"狂犬惊魂记"吗
Hey, remember, um, last night when we were talking about Cujo?
我不敢相信你没看过 你是不是有问题啊
Oh, yeah, I can't believe you haven't seen Cujo. What is wrong with you?
别紧张 它不是"大国民"
Relax, it's not like it's Citizen Kane.
你看完了"大国民"
Have you ever tried to sit through Citizen Kane?
对 它真的很无聊
Yeah, I know. It's really boring.
- 但它是名片   - 对啊
- But it's a big deal.     - Yeah.
总之 我想去租"狂犬惊魂记"
Anyway, I was thinking about renting Cujo sometime.
我们今晚一起看吧
Well, yeah, all right. Let's do it tonight.
- 你不是有约会吗    - 对
- Don't you have that big date tonight?     - Oh, right.
- 乔伊 我能问你一件事吗    - 问吧
- Hey, Joey, can I ask you something?     - Yeah.
昨晚约会后你觉不觉得怪怪的
After our date last night, did you feel a little weird?
天啊 你也是吗 我吓坏了 那是什么
Oh, my God. You did too? It freaked me out. What was that?
我不知道
I don't know.
我想应该是龙虾的问题
I'm kind of thinking it was the lobster.
对 龙虾
Oh, yeah. Yeah, the lobster.
- 我吐了一整晚   - 我也是
- I was up sick all night.     - Yeah, me too. All night.
真的吗 我没看到你
Really? How come we didn't cross paths?
对 那是因为…
Yeah, well, that's because, uh...
我都待在房里
...I stayed in my room.
你不会想看我的洗衣篮的
Yeah, you don't want to look in my hamper.
我懂了
Okay, I got that.
我要逃离那里 回到这里
I'll escape there. I'll come back here.
来吧 小精灵
All right. Come on, Ms. Pac-Man...
你是个混蛋 对吧
Well, you're just a little bitch, aren't you?
大家好
Hey, you guys?
抱歉之前我霸占着电动玩具
I'm sorry that I was hogging the game before.
天啊 你朋友名字的缩写真难听
Oh, my God, your friends have some unfortunate initials.
- 那都是钱德干的   - 钱德烂透了
- They're all Chandler.     - Chandler sucks.
- 不可能有这么厉害   - 我很厉害
- He couldn't have gotten this good.     - I did.
但那是要付出代价的
But it came at a price.
小班要过来 他不能看到这个
Ben's coming, and he can't see this.
七岁的孩子应该都看过杂交
Come on, by age 7, kids have already seen orgies.
还是只有我而已
Was it just me?
我办到了 我及时赶到
Yes, I made it! I'm on time!
好了 请大家…
Okay, why don't we all, uh...
翻到第23页…
...open our books to page 23...
你们…
...where...
你们将会看到…
...where you will see a, uh...
很多红点
...a bunch of, uh, red spots.
请大家先看一下 我要…
Okay, why don't, uh, you all start to read, while I...
你没事吗 你似乎有点心不在焉
Hey, are you all right? You seem a little distracted.
不 我没事 我只是…
No, no, I'm fine. It's just...
我能问你一件事吗
Hey, can I ask you something?
你有没有看着你认识的人…
Have you ever looked at someone that you've known for a while...
突然间有不一样的感觉
...and suddenly seen them in a different way?
你是说从背后看吗
You mean like from behind?
没错 就是那样
Yeah. Yeah. That's exactly it.
你知道吗
You know what?
有一次我从背后看这个家伙 觉得他真的很普通
One time I saw this guy from behind, and he seemed totally normal.
他一转身 我才知道他是史蒂芬·鲍德温
And then he turned around and it was Stephen Baldwin!
对 你完全了解我的意思
Ooh, yeah. So you know exactly what I'm talking about.
没错
Totally! Wow.
- 对不起   - 请便
- Would you excuse me for a sec?     - Yeah, sure.
- 菲比 你真的很厉害   - 我知道
- God, Phoebe! You're on fire!     - I know!
- 你办得到   - 别碰我
- You can do it!     - Don't touch me!
别碰她
Don't touch her!
左边 右边 右边
All right, go left! Go right! Go right!
我办不到
I can't! I can't!
不 你这个天杀的…
No! You son of a...
菲比
Phoebe!
嗨 小班 不 别看机器
Oh, hi, Ben. No, don't look at the machine!
谢天谢地 你回来了
Aah! God! Thank God you're home.
- 我在看"狂犬惊魂记"   - 你一个人
- I'm watching Cujo.     - Alone?
- 对 这只狗是怎么了    - 你看到…
- Yes! What is wrong with this dog?     - Did you get to the part...
狗自己去撞车的那一幕了吗
...where they're in the car and Cujo's throwing himself at the windshield?
不 真的 这只狗是怎么了
No. No! Seriously, what's wrong with the dog?
你怎么在家 你不是去约会了吗
What are you doing home? What happened to your date?
我们之间不来电
Oh, uh, it didn't work out.
你要跟我一起把电影看完吗
Want to watch the rest of the movie with me?
好吧
Oh, uh, okay. Yeah.
我没有想过我会这么说…
I never thought I'd say this about a movie...
但我希望这只狗死掉
...but I hope this dog dies.
你在做什么 坐在这里保护我
What are you doing over there? Come sit here. Protect me.
没问题 有何不可呢
Oh. Sure, yeah. Why not?
好吧
Okay.
- 那就是他 那就是库裘   - 我知道
- That's him, that's him! That's Cujo!     - All right, I know.
没事的
It's gonna be okay.
天啊 他现在会怎么做  我不敢看
Oh, my God. What's he gonna do now? I can't watch.
你怎么能看这个 你不害怕吗
Ugh, seriously, how can you watch this? Aren't you scared?
我怕极了
Terrified.
大家都来了吗 今天我提早到了
So is everybody here? I got here a little early, myself.
开始上课吧
Let us begin.
鸭嘴龙在两个地方被发掘
Now, the hadrosaurids have been unearthed in two main locations.
这里…
Here...
跟这里
...and here.
至于鸭嘴龙…
Now, as for the hadrosaurus...